Contact

cwongers@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/caitlinwong-3b475195 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

BLS

Nursing

ACLS

Certifications

Critical Care Registered Nurse (Adult) (CCRN-A)

Caitlin Wong

Registered Nurse at Mount Sinai Health System

Hoboken, New Jersey

Summary

RN license in New Jersey and. CCRN certified. Experience in Vascular Access Service, Cardiothoracic surgery ICU for 4 years, and telemetry/step-down for 4 years (specifically cardiac, thoracic, and vascular surgery). Traveled as RN in NYC. ACLS, and BLS certified.

Experience

Mount Sinai Health System

5 years 4 months

Vascular Access Service

January 2020 - Present (5 months)

IV insertions with ultrasound-PIVs, EDPIVs, Midlines

Intensive Care Nurse

April 2016 - January 2020 (3 years 10 months)

Cardiothoracic Surgery ICU

Registered Nurse

February 2015 - April 2016 (1 year 3 months)

Telemetry Stepdown for Thoracic and Vascular Surgery

NYU Hospital for Joint Diseases

Travel RN

October 2014 - January 2015 (4 months)

Traumatic brain injury and neuro rehab

ACCESS Healthcare Services

Travel RN

July 2014 - January 2015 (7 months)

nyc, ny

Mount Sinai Health System Travel RN July 2014 - September 2014 (3 months)

Thoracic and vascular stepdown

Capital Health System
Registered Nurse
February 2012 - July 2014 (2 years 6 months)
Cardiac telemetry

Education

East Stroudsburg University of Pennsylvania
Bachelors of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2007 - 2011)